This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting possible
reaching, we are home.
From the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that
I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But as for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you in our path.
I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that
I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But after the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
What was that ruckus?
I heard a loud noise coming from
over there Was it an intruder?
Is that it?
What the hell's going on here?
Bobbin, sir, what happened to the wall?
Don't tell us you were under attack.
Did somebody try to hurt you?
It was nothing unusual, but rest
assured, you can all take it easy.
Bobbin, sir.
There's no need to worry.
I can take care of this
little problem myself.
He won't get away with this.
I swear it!
Even the demons from
Hell itself wouldn't dare
turn down an invitation
to Mama's Tea Party.
Magic Mirror!
Thank you, Tia.
You're welcome.
Hey, uh, I think there's
something right behind Brooke.
It can't be.
This will be quite troublesome.
So what's the plan if
you need it spelled out.
That mirror leads to mama's bedroom.
So that's one of the emperors of the sea.
At the very least he's still alive.
This will be messy.
Why is he there of all places?
Yeah, why is she sleeping with him?
He seems to be deep in slumber himself.
How can he relax right now?
Hey, Brock, wake up!
No use.
Guess he can't hear you at all.
Good luck trying to
get Mama to let him go.
She adores oddities like him.
But don't fret.
I can help you out by making
her loosen up her grip.
Hey, Mama!
It's me, Barrel! Chouchou!
Chouchou!
Knock it out!
Silence them!
Let's go!
Hey, do you think she heard us?
Is she awake?
Good. Still out cold.
She, she, she knows that we're here.
Oh,
I
see.
Just a fly.
What? Who's there? The boy?
Uh, he's up!
Bear, can you hear us?
We're over here!
Oh, I see. That's fine.
The freak?
Huh? What, Mama?
We're under attack?
I need my freak! You'll go! Hey!
There you are!
Are they really that powerful?
Who are we supposed to save him?
He's just killing me!
This looks grim!
Hey, stop it!
That food doesn't belong to you!
I'm sorry, boy.
But there's somebody really
important I've got to give this to.
Hmm.
I think this baby needs some more hair.
How's this, then?
Eating improvement? For sure.
Way more convincing.
Where did you even find this guy, anyway?
He's from the execution grounds here.
The Afro is made of
seaweed from the kitchen.
All right, our friend here is good to go.
Wow, he looks exactly like Brook. Totally.
If we can just switch him
out with the real Brook,
I don't think she'll
even notice he's gone.
Good work.
Now if we place Barrel at
the midpoint between worlds,
we should be able to easily enter and
exit the giant mirror as we please.
Huh?
Damn it, I'll make them pay.
And with that, I believe
we're all set now.
Shall we get to work?
Let the Brook Rescue Mission commence!
Challenge one!
Wish me luck! Here I go!
Remember, you can't make any noise.
You can count on me!
Ahhhh...
Alright, wait for me, Brooke.
I'm coming.
Don't scream!
I was scared!
So incredibly scared!
Are you two okay?
Somebody else needs to do it then. Let me!
I'll make sure to get the job done!
Challenge two!
Oh!
That a girl!
Brooke!
Brooke, wake up!
You gotta go, sleepyhead! Oh, no!
The bubble is getting
bigger! Leave now! Ah!
Did she notice?
It's looking right at me.
Huh?
What'd you do?
A stuffed bunny defense.
I won't fall for that.
Oh, never mind.
I guess it's just a stuffed bunny.
Wait, that really worked? Hurry!
This is your chance, Carrot!
I'll do it this time.
It's that damn fly again.
What an annoying pet!
I'm scared!
So incredibly scared!
Alright, who's up next?
What an embarrassing display.
Very well.
I guess it's up to me.
Challenge three!
Brooke!
It's time to head out!
Come on!
She rolled over!
Did that wake him?
No.
He's out of Big Mom's hands now.
Okay, let me have a shot.
Challenge four.
Brock! Hey, get up!
Hiya, Brock!
Huh?
It's me, Nami!
What now?
Are you still here?
Oh, no!
I'm trying to save you stupid fly!
Heavenly!
Fire!
Nice work!
That was way too close.
Jinbei, thank you.
Mission accomplished!
Where?
That was scary!
Oh, man!
It seems like you really
messed these guys up.
Good thing you said your goodbyes.
It turns out we're holding Straw Hat and
the Cat Burglar captive in the library.
Luffy fought all night against one of
Big Mom's strongest generals to get here.
He's in no shape to do this,
Luffy, you told me you'd be waiting.
Where the hell are you!
Luffy!
I'm utterly shocked!
Ah, ah, ah, about everything!
Do not have it, Dr. Speed!
You picked the worst type thing out!
I sincerely thank you.
All that matters is that you're safe now.
Yes, I thought I was dead for certain.
Or rather, double dead.
With the heightened security,
I should have realized sooner
that we would be unable
to make a copy of the Road
Poneglyph on this trip.
It's my fault for pushing it.
I needlessly put your life at risk.
My apologies.
Don't be ridiculous.
You selflessly stuck your neck out for us.
Had it not been for your bold idea
to infiltrate as a two-man team,
we never would have had
this golden opportunity.
If we attempted to take the stone
rubbings on any other occasion,
there would have been no way
to avoid an Alto pirate war.
We had to try.
Despite the poor odds,
it was our only option.
Here, the copy.
Anyway, I can't tell you how glad I
am that you got away safely, Pedro.
The copy I wish our plan hadn't
been so fraught with peril,
but asking you to act as bait
was all I could scrape together.
Hold on—is this what I think it is? Brook?
It's a copy of the poneglyph.
I
made it with seconds to spare, just as
I finished transcribing the third sheet.
sheet And out of the blue
came Big Mom herself.
I can't believe our eyes!
You Karoo got past all the guards?
You even got past all
of the sweet generals?
Do you Karoo even know
what the other emperors of
the sea would do to get
their hands on her road,
Poneglyph?
And this is it?
Um, yes.
What?
He not only reached, but
copied our poneglyph?
A miracle!
Oftentimes,
even Big Mom's own beloved family is not
permitted in the treasure repository.
You really are something else!
Perhaps now I'm worthy of a panty-peak?
Hey!
He's already hurt!
Amazing!
That takes care of one
of our big objectives!
That means all that's left
is for us to grab Sanji!
Thank you.
No one knows where they are!
Sorry, miss!
They did pass by me a while ago, though.
Yeah, but they're off here now!
What about Sanji's room?
No, just some weird guy that's
made himself quite comfortable.
That's it.
I think I know where he is.
He has to be outside where
there are no mirrors.
And just earlier, Luffy
met Sanji in a field.
And they got in a big fight.
What could they be fighting
over in a time like this?
I would like to know too.
Sanji has assumed his position
as a son of the Vinsmoke family.
I know.
He must have had a very
compelling reason to come here.
So taking him back may not be so simple.
But if we are going to retrieve
him, we must make haste.
I was going to tell you all
once everyone was together,
but perhaps now is best
regrettably the wedding ceremony
planned for tomorrow is not
going to be a peaceful one.
What does that mean?
Your crew traveled here to whole cake island
with peckham's as your guide, correct?
Oh yeah, peckham's is he okay?
We got separated from him
right after we got here.
Yes,
he is fine but he got
involved in a conspiratorial
plot that nearly resulted
in him being fed to sharks.
That's wild, if I hadn't
noticed what was happening,
he would be dead.
You're not people, you're like monsters!
Oh, that's pathetic.
Barmaids really should be able
to hold their liquor better.
If they were going to send us girls, I
wish they gave us Sanji's Gourmet instead.
Yeah, the one named Nami, huh?
We all love a hot-blooded woman, right?
Word is Big Mom's already captured her.
Hey pups, let's see if we can
work out a trade for her tomorrow.
Alright, that's enough drinking for now.
The real festivities will
take place after the ceremony.
Our alliance with Big Mom will turn
us into a truly formidable force.
And soon we will conquer
the North Blue once again.
The same countries that
scored and insult us now?
will be groveling at the
feet of the Germa kingdom.
Our day of revenge is finally upon us.
Tomorrow, we celebrate.
I never imagined that
the embarrassment of the
Vinsmoke family would
prove to be so useful.
Even a failure is good for something.
Uh-huh.
With Sanji used his bait,
we sure hooked a Wapol.
Just think of when our foes see Big
Mom's flag on the German Armada.
They'll all turn tail.
It'll be glorious.
The seas will be ours just
as they were meant to be.
Now a toast to dear Sanji.
Oh, come on, do we gotta?
To that piece of crap!
To the useful failure!
Cheers!
It's imperative that
the Vinsmokes don't come
into contact with anyone
until tomorrow's party.
Understood.
We already have guards on the third floor
overseeing the room that Reiju's in.
Take extra precaution. Yes, sir.
The Vinsmokes will meet
their maker as planned.
Don't say it out loud, you imbecile.
Damn it.
Curse them, you bastards!
Leave my sight.
Bunch of low-class pirates.
It's that Sanchi.
You moron.
I didn't tell you to wait for me.
I'm not leaving.
Eat whatever's salvageable.
Dinner.
I dropped it on my way here.
It's crushed and was rained on, too.
It's just another failure.
It's yummy!
This is the best food ever.
This is cool.
It's all our favorites in one lunchbox.
You've got to make this
for the whole crew.
Oh, man.
Yum, yum.
Stop lying.
Ah!
That hit the spot!
I thought I was going to shrivel up! Ah!
Are you done?
Uh-huh. Good. Then leave.
What do you mean?
We're going back!
First, the captain of my own ship
came all the way here for me.
And not only did I insult
and try to hurt him,
but he also gave me no
resistance whatsoever.
That alone is more than enough reason
for me to not return to your crew.
Secondly, remember the old
geezer who saved my life?
You know, the one I'm deeply indebted to?
while he and the baratier,
the place where I grew up,
are being held hostage in case I run.
That's also why I can't back
out of the ceremony tomorrow.
Reason three, the evil family I'm related
to is walking right into Big Bomb's trap.
They'll all be murdered
in a matter of hours.
If you don't run away, the whole
situation will tidy up quite nicely.
Realistically, I know they're monsters.
I don't owe them a thing.
The thought of them makes me sick.
You've always been a failure, Sanji.
You deserve to rot and die.
No matter what, if anyone
ever asks about your family,
you must never tell
them who your father is.
Having you as a son is my greatest shame.
But despite all that crap...
And the torment.
I can't turn my back on those bastards.
that's why I can't leave
here with you sorry
I just can't and there's
no way to fix this
So there you have it.
Now get lost.
Oh, my God.
How do you really feel?
Just say it!
Hey, Sanji!
I'm hungry!
Get to cooking already, you fool!
So, Sanji, what you gonna make us today?
Which one of you swiped the food?
You're all guilty as hell.
As your punishment, you'll
go to bed with no dinner.
Fine, Luffy,
I give up to go
home to the sunny.
But I can't muster the
courage to run away.
Once the wedding begins,
I can't stop any of it.
Especially not on my own.
I despise my whole family.
They've always treated me like dirt.
But I...
I still want to save those scumbags.
I get it.
That's who you are!
You have us, Sanji, and
we'll crash that party!
Thank you.